# MARIA LEAVILL V. PABLO

Blk 15 Lt 4 Northgate 1 Springtown Brgy. Bucal Tanza, Cavite Email:leavillverdan@ymail.com

Contact number: +63938-217-7878



## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

College graduate with experience as Accounting Staff. To accept any position of which I am qualified that provides opportunities for additional training and learnings, I would like to utilize my skills and experience to contribute in the organization in achieving their goals and objectives.

## **EDUCATION**

**DEGREE:** Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, major in Accounting Management *At Sacred Heart College, Lucena City* 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Casino Bar Phils., Inc. Accounting Staff May 2013-March 2020 Pasay City

Casamia Furniture Center Inc. SM Corporate Office Accounting Staff October 2012-March 2013 Pasay City

Raquel Pawnshop Inc. Project-Based Auditor April 2011-March 2012

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

Age: 29 years old
Sex: Female
Civil Status: Married
Birth Date: April 11, 1991
Nationality: Filipino
Weight: 50 kls.
Height: 4'8

# **CHARACTER REFERENCES**

## **NOEL ALIDO**

Art Director VG Group of Companies Contact #: +63966-140-2199

## KRIS JOY GALLENERO

Bookkeeper Casino Bar Phils.Inc.

Contact #: +63995-855-1996

## MARIEBETH N. DOMINGO

HRD/Admin Officer
VG Group of Companies
Contact #: +63922-828-5604

I hereby certify that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

MARIA LEAVILL V. PABLO

Applicant